A Finding Aid to the James Graham & Sons Gallery Records, 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011, bulk 1950s-1980s, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
James Graham & Sons records
1821
1815
circa 1896-2011
AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
95.2 Linear feet
The records of the New York City gallery James Graham & Sons measure 95.2 linear feet and date from 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011 (bulk 1950s-1980s). The collection generally documents the gallery's contemporary art department during the time in which Robert Claverhouse Graham, Sr. worked at the gallery (1940-1979); records prior to 1954 are sparse and scattered. Gallery records include artist files; correspondence; exhibition files; financial records; inventory records; printed materials; sales, loans, and consignment records; scrapbooks; and photographic materials. Also found are records from Coe Kerr Gallery regarding exhibitions.
James Graham & Sons
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The James Graham & Sons records were donated in three accessions in 2007, 2008, and 2012 by Priscilla Caldwell and Jay Grimm of James Graham & Sons.
Related Material
Among the other resources relating to James Graham & Sons in the Archives of American Art is an oral history interview with Robert Claverhouse Graham, November 19, 1976, and the David Herbert papers, 1950-1995.
Restrictions on Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment. Artwork Files (Boxes 63-71, 94) and some photographic materials (Box 93 and 101) require written permission to access.
Historical Note
The James Graham & Sons gallery has been owned and managed by the Graham family in New York City since 1857. Throughout its history, the gallery has specialized in decorative arts, antiques, and 19th-early 20th century and contemporary American art.
In 1857, Samuel Graham founded a gallery at 66 Third Street and specialized in furniture. Graham was joined by his son James in the 1880s and expanded the business to include antiques and decorative arts. James A. Graham, the third generation Graham, joined the gallery in the early 20th century. James Graham and antiques dealer Marshall Clapp created Clapp & Graham in 1914, a partnership which was dissolved around 1940.
James R. Graham, the fourth generation Graham, joined the gallery in 1937, followed by his brother Robert Claverhouse Graham, Sr. in 1940. The gallery was then named James Graham & Sons and was located at 514 Madison Avenue. At this time, the gallery specialized in bronzes, ceramics, silver, sculptures, and 19th-early 20th century American art. Robert C. Graham, Sr. introduced modern American art, especially The Eight, into the gallery's inventory.
In 1955, the gallery moved to 1014 Madison Avenue, where it remained until the late 2000s. That same year, Graham opened its first contemporary department with Albert Duveen. Duveen-Graham Modern Art gallery was based on the third floor of the Madison Avenue building and dealt solely in contemporary art until its closing in 1958. Robert C. Graham, Jr. (Robin) joined the gallery in 1963, becoming the fifth generation Graham to run the family business. The gallery is currently located at 32 East 67th Street.
Betsy Fahlman's "James Graham & Sons: A Century and a Half in the Art Business" (2007) was a valuable resource in constructing this Historical Note.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the New York City gallery James Graham & Sons measure 95.2 linear feet and date from 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011 (bulk 1950s-1980s). The collection generally documents the gallery's contemporary art department during the time in which Robert Claverhouse Graham, Sr. worked at the gallery (1940-1979); records prior to 1954 are sparse and scattered. Gallery records include artist files; correspondence; exhibition files; financial records; inventory records; printed materials; sales, loans, and consignment records; scrapbooks; and photographic materials. Also found are records from Coe Kerr Gallery regarding exhibitions of artwork by Jamie Wyeth, and to a lesser extent, Andrew and N.C. Wyeth.
Over the years, the gallery changed names and established contemporary art departments. In addition to records of James Graham & Sons, the collection holds the records of Duveen-Graham Modern Art (in partnership with Albert Duveen), Graham Gallery, Graham Modern, JG|Contemporary, and, to a lesser extent, The Clapp and Graham Co.
Alphabetical files are a mix of business correspondence and business records. The bulk of the series contains correspondence with galleries, museums, other institutions, and, to a lesser extent, clients regarding sales, consignments, and loans of artwork. Also found are materials relevant to the daily operations of the gallery, including correspondence, subject files, and scattered financial, business and legal records.
Exhibition files provide scattered documentation of the gallery's exhibitions through catalogs, clippings, correspondence, guest books, notes, photographs, press materials, price lists, and sales receipts and other financial records.
Artists' Files document the numerous artists who have been represented by the gallery, especially modern American artists. Folders for each artist can contain a variety of materials, including correspondence with the artist or with institutions regarding consignments, loans, sales and exhibitions; photographic materials primarily of artwork; sales invoices; exhibition catalogs, postcards, and other printed materials; press releases; magazine and newspaper clippings; price lists; artist binders; and research materials on artists and artwork. Also found are some subject files, per original arrangement. There is extensive material related to artists Carmen Cicero, Susan Crile, Elaine De Kooning's portrait of President John F. Kennedy, Edwin Dickinson, muralist Seymour Fogel, Nancy Fried, Irving Kriesberg, Gari Melchers, Jonathan Santlofer, Reeve Schley, Peter Stevens, Joan Thorne, and Selina Trieff.
Artwork files document sales, consignments, and loans of artwork primarily from the mid-1980s to 2000s. Materials include agreements and contracts; condition reports; correspondence; invoices and receipts; photographs of artwork; shipping records; and photocopied printed material and other documentation. This series requires written permission from the donor in order to access.
Sales records from 1959-1984 (missing 1974) are found in the Financial Records series. Also found are check stub books from the mid-late 1950s; price lists; records for the Four Seasons Charter Corp.; and scattered banking, consignment, tax, and other financial records. Inventory cards from mid-1950s-1970s and inventory lists, often with notations and prices, are found in the series Inventory Records.
Coe Kerr Gallery Records regarding the Wyeths document Jamie Wyeth's exhibitions primarily from the mid-1970s-early 1980s. Also found is limited material regarding Andrew Wyeth and N.C. Wyeth. Materials include correspondence, photographs, exhibition printed materials, and extensive newspaper clippings.
There are exhibition catalogs, books, announcements, magazines, clippings, postcards, posters and other printed materials related to artists, John Graham & Sons exhibitions, and exhibitions by Graham artists held at other galleries and museums. Also found is an 1815 fifty cent note which was redeemed in 1821.
Seven scrapbooks document discrete aspects of the business, including the gallery's advertising, participation in an art fair, and the careers of artists Guy Coheleach and Van Dearing Perrine. Materials housed in the scrapbooks include clippings, catalogs, photographs, and other printed materials.
Photographic Materials include mostly black and white photographs, negatives, slides and transparencies of artwork; scattered photographs of installations, artists, and the gallery; and a handful of personal snapshots. The bulk of the photographs are undated, but were likely printed between 1950s-1990s.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 10 series:
Series 1: Alphabetical Files, circa 1896, 1902-1999, bulk 1955-1986 (Boxes 1-15; 15 linear feet)
Series 2: Exhibition Files, 1912, 1947-2004 (Boxes 16-24; 8 linear feet)
Series 3: Artists' Files, circa 1907-2006, bulk 1955-1999 (Boxes 24-62, 95-96; 39.1 linear feet)
Series 4: Artwork Files, circa early 1900s-2011, bulk mid-1980s-2009 (Boxes 63-71, 94, 101; 9.3 linear feet)
Series 5: Financial Records, circa 1937-1993 (Boxes 72-76, 96; 4.5 linear feet)
Series 6: Inventory Records, circa 1954-1993 (Boxes 76-78, 96; 2.1 linear feet)
Series 7: Coe Kerr Gallery Records Regarding Wyeths, 1964-1988 (Boxes 78-80, 97; 2.7 linear feet)
Series 8: Printed Materials, 1815, 1821, 1949-2006 (Boxes 81-82, 97; 2.1 linear feet)
Series 9: Scrapbooks, 1897-1990s (Boxes 82, 98-100; 0.9 linear feet)
Series 10: Photographic Materials, 1929-1990s (Boxes 83-93, 96, 100-101; 11.5 linear feet)
Cicero, Carmen, 1926-; Coe Kerr Gallery; Coheleach, Guy; Crile, Susan, 1942-; De Kooning, Elaine; Dickinson, Edwin Walter, 1891-1978; Duveen, Albert; Duveen-Graham (Gallery); Fogel, Seymour, 1911-1984; Fried, Nancy; Graham Gallery; Graham Modern (Gallery); Graham, Robert Claverhouse, 1913-1994; Kriesberg, Irving, 1919-; Melchers, Gari, 1860-1932; Perrine, Van Dearing, 1869-1955; Santlofer, Jonathan, 1946-; Schley, Reeve, 1936-; Stevens, Peter; Thorne, Joan, 1943-; Trieff, Selina, 1934-; Wyeth, Andrew, 1917-; Wyeth, Jamie, 1946-; Wyeth, N. C. (Newell Convers), 1882-1945; Art galleries, Commercial--New York (State)--New York; Art--Economic aspects; Painting--United States; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Sculpture--United States; Visitors' books
- Alphabetical Files, bulk 1955-1986; 1902-1999; circa 1896; Series 1; 15 Linear feet Boxes 1-15
  Scope and Contents note
  The bulk of Alphabetical Files is a mix of business correspondence and business records. The correspondence is mostly with galleries, museums, universities, and, to a lesser extent, clients concerning sales, consignments, loans and exhibitions. Also found are general inquiries to the gallery; subject files related to exhibitions and the daily operation of the gallery; some bills and receipts; and scattered business and legal records.
  Upon processing, the original arrangement of materials found in this series was unknown. The processing archivist chose to describe the series "Alphabetical Files" as portions of the mixed materials were often arranged alphabetically.
  Arrangement note
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - A Correspondence, 1955-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Accademia Dei Virtuosi Al Pantheon, 1974; 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advertising, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advertising, Sculpture Wanted, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Akron Art Institute, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Albany Institute of History and Art, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Albright Art Gallery, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Albright-Knox Gallery, 1961-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
  - Larry Aldrich Museum, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Allentown Art Museum, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Altschul, Arthur, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Abstract Artists, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Federation of Arts, 1954-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
  - American Masters Gallery, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American-Scottish Foundation, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
  - Anschutz Gallery, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Appraisals, circa 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
  - [Appraisals], Dr. James R. Herz, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - [Appraisals, McCormick], 1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Appraisals, Lawrence Rockefeller, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - [Appraisals and Recommendations], 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Architectural Ideas, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Archives of American Art, 1954-1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - [Aronson, Adam], 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Art Center in La Jolla, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Art Gallery of Ontario, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Art Institute of Chicago, 1956-1982 (Box 1, Folder 36-39)
  - Art International, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Art Table, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Artificial Upwelling, 1986; 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - The Artis Group, Inc., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Artists' Biographies, 1902-1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Artists' Biographies, 1919-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Artists' Biographies, Graham Modern], circa 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Artwork at Framer's/Restorer's, 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Auburn University, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - [Augsbury, Frank A., Jr.], 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - [Avery, Sid, Mr. and Mrs.], 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - B Bills, 1955-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - B Correspondence, 1954-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8-12)
  - B Correspondence With Museums, Galleries and Collectors, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Babcock Galleries, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Franz Bader Gallery (Washington, D.C.), 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1956-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - Bank Tortola, 1970s-1980s (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bankers Trust, 1957-1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - B.C. Silver Mine Norquest Goat Ridge, 1972-1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Beadleston Gallery, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Beard Art Galleries (Minneapolis, MN), 1956-1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bennington College, 1973-1976; 1958 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Berger Art Conservation, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Berry Hill Gallery, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Big Brothers, Inc., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Birmingham Museum, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bono, Sonny and Cher, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bortman Silver Collection, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Boston Athenaeum, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Boston Fine Arts Festival, 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Boston University Gallery, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Boswell Energy Corporation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Braclay Gallery, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Brandywine River, 1976; 1974 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Brixey, Ms., 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Brooklyn College, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1955-1969 (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
  - Brown, Oliver, The Leicester Galleries, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Building Permits, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Butler Institute, 1957-1969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Byron Gallery, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - C Correspondence, 1954-1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - C Correspondence, 1955-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
  - [Cane, Melville (Estate of)], circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1956-1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Museum, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Carone Gallery, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Choate School, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1976; 1968; 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Circker's Hayes Storage, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Citadel, 1972; 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - City of St. Louis, 1956-1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Clan Graham Society, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - [Clark, William G.], 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The Cleveland Institute of Art, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1956-1974 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
  - [Coles, William], 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1957; 1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Columbia Museum of Art, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - [Consignments], 1961-1973; 1944 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - [Consignments], List of Paintings on Consignment to Graham Gallery, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Contemporary Gallery, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Cooper Hewitt Museum, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1956-1975 (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
  - Correspondence (1974), 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
  - Correspondence and Memos, Miscellaneous, 1967-1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Printed Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1964-1973 (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
  - [Correspondence, Cameron Shay?], 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - [Correspondence, Cameron Shay?], 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Country Art Gallery, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cummer Gallery, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Curl Gallery, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - [Cutler, Mitchell], 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - D Bills, 1955-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - D Correspondence, 1965-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8-12)
  - D General, 1955-1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dallas North Galleries, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bernard Danenberg Gallery, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Davies Gallery, 1958; undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Terry, Personal, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Dayton Art Institute, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - [Dayton, Bruce], 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - De Cordova Museum, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dead Files (Jan. 1973), Second Floor, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - [Dead Files and Memos], 1960-1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Dead Letters, General (Alphabetical), 1964; 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Dead Memos, 1965-1978 (Box 4, Folder 25-27)
  - Dead Memos and Receipts (1979), 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Delaware Art Museum, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Isaac Delgado Museum, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Denison University, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Denver Art Gallery, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Des Moines Art Center, 1974-1975; 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Sid Deutsch Gallery, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Deville Galleries, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - M.H. de Young Memorial Museum, 1977; 1974 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Discovery Gallery, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Dorsky Gallery, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Douglas Drake Gallery, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - The Drawing Room, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - [Drawings], circa 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Contains artwork
  - Duveen-Graham, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - E Bills, 1955-1963 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - E Correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 4, Folder 44-46)
  - E General, 1971-1976; 1955-1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Earle, Constance, "Sir Walter Scott in the Rhymer's Glen" (Landseer), 1985; 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Educational Institute for Learning and Research, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Elvehjem Art Center, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Michael M. Engel Associates, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - [Equitable Real Estate], 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Equity Appraisal, circa 1974-1980s (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - [Ertegun, Ahmet], 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Europe, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - European Trip, 1968-1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Schedules, 1956-1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Schedules [Sent to Magazines], 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - F Bills, 1955-1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - F Correspondence, 1962-1985 (Box 5, Folder 13-15)
  - F General, 1955-1961; 1967-1976; 1944 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Fairfield University, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Fakes We Have Seen, 1978-1979; 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Linda Farris Gallery, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - [Fehrer, Elizabeth], 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Field, Marshall, III, 1974-1982 (Box 5, Folder 22-23)
  - [Figgie, Harry, Jr., Mrs.], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Finch College Museum, 1970; 1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Flags, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - [Fogel, Seymour (Estate of)], 1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Fogg Museum, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - [Fokine, Peter], 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Forsythe Gallery, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Fort Lauderdale Museum, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Forum Gallery, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - The Four Seasons Charter Corp., Correspondence (1965-1971) (Box 5, Folder 33-38)
  - [The Four Seasons Charter Corp., Yacht "Stranger"], 1972 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - [The Four Seasons Charter Corp., Yacht "Stranger," Photographs], 1966 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Frames, 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - [Freeman, Howard], 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Frick Gallery, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - G Correspondence, 1962-1986 (Box 6, Folder 3-7)
  - G General, 1967-1977; 1955-1962 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Galerie Agora, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Galerie Arnoldi-Livie, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gallery of Fine Comic Art, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gallery Gemini Inc., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gallery Notes, circa late 1980s (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - [Ganz, Julian, Jr.], 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Gemeentelijk Museum, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - General, Topics for Contemporary Floor, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Genesis Gallery, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Georgia Museum of Art, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Otto Gerson Gallery, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Gimpel Fils, 1954-1957 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Glenbow-Alberta Institute, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - [Goldyne, Joseph], 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - [Gordon, Harry B.], 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Gotham Book Mart and Gallery, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Graham Gallery Artists Distribution, circa 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Graham Gallery, Ltd., 1967-1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Graham Gallery [Regarding Exhibitions], 1958-1977 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Graham Geneology, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Graham, James, Beginning Aug. 1983, 1983-1989; 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Graham, Robert C., 1974 RCG After Z in File Drawer, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Graham, Robert C., Paintings [Personal?], circa 1956-1986 (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
    Disassembled binder
  - Graham, Robert C., Personal Since March 9, 1974, 1973-1975; 1966 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Graham, Robert C., Since Jan. 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Graham, Robert C., Since March 1976, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
  - Graham, Robert C., Sr., 1983-1988; 1975 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Graham, Robert C., Sr., Personal Business, 1979-1983; 1962 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Grand Central Galleries, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - [Grayson, Frederic], 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Greggs, circa 1960s (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Grey Gallery, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - [Griscom, Bronson], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Grolier Club, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Guerney's, 1970s; 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Guggenheim Museum, 1953-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
  - Guiyermo Gallery, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gunn and Latchford, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - H Correspondence, 1965-1983 (Box 7, Folder 12-17)
  - H General, 1955-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
  - Haefelin, Joseph C., 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hall Galleries, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Hallmark Art Restoration, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hamilton College, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - [Hamilton, William K.B.], 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hammer Gallery, 1956; 1962 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - [Harrison, Alfred C., Jr.], 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Dalzell Hatfield Gallery (Los Angeles, CA), 1956 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Hecksher Museum, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - [Hem, Burton L.], 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hirschl & Adler Galleries, 1975; 1972 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hirshhorn Museum, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - [Hitara], 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Hofstra University, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - [Holcomb, Warren L.], 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - [Holt, Henry, Jr.], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - [Hoopes, Donelson], 1978 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - [Horn, Robert A.], 1978-1985 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - J.L. Hudson Gallery, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - The Hudson River School, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hunter Gallery, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Hyde Collection, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - I Bills, 1955-1963 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - I Correspondence, 1965-1981 (Box 7, Folder 44-46)
  - I General, 1955-1976 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Ideas, 1958-1966 (Box 7, Folder 48-50)
  - [Igoe, H.E., Jr.], 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 51)